

Hello! I'm a digital maestro skilled in web development, C++ programming, website design, and captivating content creation. With experience as a Digital Marketing Head at Derma Session and a social media handler for Mona's Crafted Cakes, I specialize in crafting memorable digital experiences. Let's embark on an exciting journey to make waves in the digital world together!



+92-3084776010



DHA PHASE 4 Lahore



aymanasim26@gmail.com

Ayman Asim

Digital Marketing Specialist

Skills

- Graphic & Web Design
- Wordpress Expert
- C++ Developer
- Photography & Editing
- Advertising & Branding
- Conceptualization & Copywriting
- Teaching

Work Experience

2017-2020

Monas Crafted Cakes

Social Media Manager

 Handling social media campaign and managing team to handling social media timeline upload

2020-present

Derma-Session

Digital Marketing Manager

 Managing overseas company digital marketing strategies to reach more client in website and social media

Education History

2017-2020

Bricks

O/Levels

2020-2022

Roots Millennium FWS

A/Levels

2022-

FAST NUCES

• Bs Data Sciences